Music
Please subscribe to our channel!
Oh no, it moved!
It's been a lot of fun!
Hey!
It moved!
My hands are freezing
Hey...
You made a lot of noise.
But you know what?
I'm still interested in a seven-person showdown.
So, 2024.
It's like... one day at the gym.
Yeah.
A gymnasium.
Take a day.
I'd like to do some kind of confrontation type thing.
Maybe we can do something about allergies.
Let's plan something like that.
Yeah, let's do that.
So, back to the room this time.
The last thing I want to do is...
Kendama.
Wow, that's nice.
This one, too.
Yes!
I thought a kendama showdown would be nice... but for the first game of the new year, I'd like to strengthen the bonds between the seven members of the Genshiken club.
And I want to make sure that we do.
I'd like to do a challenge for all seven of us in a row.
Who's good at kendama? -Anyone confident?
But isn't Takato really good? -Takato, can you bring me a sword ball?
No, no, sorry, I am, but you just raised your hand.
But I'm splitting my own hand right now. - No, no, no...
Hey, can I see your territory one more time? -Sure.
May I? -The kendama is... certified.
Certified. - I think it's certified.
I can't tell from the sound. - He's got a good vibe.
Oh, man... - I'm gonna have to get you a drink. I'll be right with you, sir.
What? Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
It's over, it's over. - It's over. - Oh, my God.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God! Wow! -Sword company!
Berry gee-fingers fly.
Brutiee...
Akane Iwamoto wufull What?
I was defending something, and I looked at it.
Wow. - This? Yeah.
Eeeee! -Eeeeeeeee!
Shannon!
Mama, ma'am, ma'am, methe enough.
Oh, that's great!
Nakamura, that means we have a member who can do kendama!
No, that's... - No, that's a strong gender too.
. Pooh!
Even Takamichi can play with his own sword. - I thought it was his own sword.
And mouth go...
Mouth go...
I'm not sure... It's like... it's natural that you can do that.
I know, I know.
And yet it's so entre...
Oh...
Huh?
Wow!
Nice. You're making the most of it. You're making the most of it.
Wooeeeeeeee!
Ehhhhhhhhh, Ministry podcasts
Highway
That's just plain awesome.
I'm going to challenge you guys, where are you going to challenge me?
If the members are so good at it, let's go for the tip of the sword!
Kensaki?
Let's try a platter.
Let's all practice once.
One at a time, one at a time.
Let's see how good you are. On the merit side.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's how we'll judge you.
Oh, good!
Good!
Good, good, good.
Oh, oh, okay.
Oh, Mr. Kato, you already did. Thank you very much.
Thank you
The limit is the limit is the limit
You can't drop it once.
Let's put it in one plate at a time, until you miss.
Oh, oh okay
Oh, that one, that one
Oh, that, that, that...
It's hard.
It's hard to make a sword ball.
Thank you very much.
This one.
Yes, sir.
I'd like you to put it all in there.
Let's take this one as an example of a success story.
Isn't it hard to make a small plate? -Small plates are hard.
Oh, my God! -That's great.
So, can I use a regular sword for the last part?
Just a sword? -Just a sword.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. - Is it a sword?
It's called a sword. - No, you can spin it.
Can I turn it? -Can I spin it?
Yeah! -That's great!
Whoo! -Oh, my God!
That feels good.
Masaya, you're doing good, aren't you? -That's good, Masaya.
Oh, yeah! -Oh, yeah?
Okay, let's do a small plate.
Oh, that's close! It's not that easy, but... Oh, that's too bad! It's not easy, but...
Sometimes it's the best I can do... this kind of thing.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Thank you very much.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
You're all tangled up.
I've always wanted to try it.
Now, in light of this, what do we do?
What do we do?
I just tried it. I don't think I can do it.
If it turns out to be impossible, it'll be a disaster.
But you said you wouldn't give up this year.
That's right.
It's your turn. It's your turn.
Order.
We're gonna have to be really strict about the order.
I'm sure some of us can make it on the last day.
But, you know, I can do numbers and swords.
I can do the sword.
It's all about concentration.
I don't know. I'm not good at it. I'm good at it.
Let's break it down into "bad at" and "good at.
I see.
For me, it's a good start.
If I succeed a couple of times...
There's a lot of pressure, right?
That's why.
It makes you nervous. - It makes you push yourself. - It makes you push yourself.
I want the best player to go first.
Okay, then. - On the contrary. That's true.
Are you sure, Ryota? Let the top guy go first. - Ryota. - Ryota.
Okay, then... - First things first. - Okay, then...
Here's the challenge. -Okay
KENTAKO Seven in a row, please.
Yes, Matsukura, if you're at the top, you can decide. - That's right.
They've all succeeded already. - That's not strange.
The challenge is to see who can do better. - Right.
Ryota, please. - Matsukura, I'll go right away. Ryota-san, please! -Ah, Matsukura, I'll be there as soon as I can, won't I?
Everything's decided at the beginning.
The most important thing is to turn it.
You turn it. - You turn it.
OK!
The first seven who succeed are the winners. - OK, OK, OK!
See you later. - Hey! - Nakagawa, you're so calm!
That was good at the end. - What? What are you doing?
Okay, okay, okay.
It's the first time. - It's the first time.
Everyone pull over.
Oh! -That's great! -That's so easy to see.
It's a sequence. - My body...
All I have to do is keep going.
Okay, okay.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Ah... -Ah...
Nice legs
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
No.
Here it comes.
It's so cool!
It doesn't turn.
It's my first time!
My first kumquat!
The first time I played kendama.
The best looking kendama
Kendama.
Down indoors, it's kendama.
Oh, my God!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's connect, connect, connect.
Let's get our hearts in the right place.
Just like soccer.
Oh, my God. Wow.
Yes, sir.
Yay!
Yes!
Three in a row.
Oh, yeah.
Good, good, good.
Staff OK!
Come on, Yang Yang! Fight!
cardiac
I love Matsumura, you can do it.
Next!
Next! Next!
Come on, come on.
Please, please, please, please.
Last Last
Oh, shit!
Aaaaah!
rate
wh
flew
Tanaka
Osaka.
The string, the string
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Osaka-san. Osaka-san.
Whoa, there it is.
Concentrate, Osaka-san.
Oh!
No, there? There?
Well, I'll just...
No, seriously.
It's too loose.
I mean, you were right, but they were scoring.
Wow!
Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah!
This is pretty bad for me.
I've never been on one of those before.
What? Why? I could have done it.
Please don't do that.
Come on. Calm down.
Oh!
This is bad.
I know, I know, I know.
That one, seriously. Concentrate.
Now, first of all, you need to stop right here and look at where you are.
Let me see it right here. Let me see it right here.
Let me show you this. Let me show you this.
Go for the ride!
Let yourself get on. Let yourself get on.
I'm the support, I don't care if you're listening or not.
I don't care if you're listening or not, you can do it.
Oh!
It's Genta!
Just now... just now...
You took it for a second, didn't you?
What just happened?
Are you serious?
It's all in one piece.
What?
I'm kind of happy about that.
No, no, no, no, no, you're right.
If anything, I think I kind of fell for it.
No, wait.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Joon-kun, Joon-kun.
I'll do it when you say so.
It's hard, it's hard, it's hard, it's hard!
The way you hold it, the way you hold it
The way you hold it, like this, I'll support it
Stiff! Stick to it.
Joon, I'll do it where you said.
Not exactly.
It's all of it. I'm done.
Then stop with Kent.
Oh, yeah!
Yay! Yay!
Oh, my God, it's finally here.
I'm finally here.
Come on, please.
Come on.
Oh, oh, beautiful.
Oh, yeah!
Oh, thank you!
All that's left is...
All we have to do is make it work.
I didn't expect you to be the last.
Surprisingly, I'm the last one.
Are you sure you want to go next time?
Yeah! -You sure you want to go?
You're going? -Go to Osaka. Go to Osaka.
Ryuta, last one? -Let's do it for the last time.
I'm most nervous about this. - This is the most nervous I've ever been in Osaka.
Oh! Here comes Matsukura! -Here it is!
That's the second oak! -That hurts. - Second orc.
Hold on, I'm going with Ryuta.
Ryuta, OK!
Ryuta, please! Please! Please!
Go Ryuta! Ryuga's coming!
Ryuga, please!
Ryuga did it!
Ryuga's good!
Ryuga is done! Ryuga was good!
I'm glad Ryuga did it!
I'm glad Ryuga won!
It was long! It was long!
It was fun!
How was it? This month How was it? This month
We've been bonding since the beginning of the year, haven't we?
We even had a tournament!
I think it was a great first month of the year!
For sure!
How was it? I feel like I'm getting better at Kendama.
In today's time...
So, let's finish up, Mr. Jun.
Please let me see you!
Swords? The last one.
Sword?
So, if I fail or succeed...
I can fade away.
To the year 2024.
Thank you!
Thank you very much!